Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY FILE, 1981-1987 (Boxes 302-367)
  - Speeches and engagements
    - Wedding of Bernadette Casey (daughter of WJC) and Owen T. Smith, Old Westbury, New York, 1985 December 7 (Box-folder 311: 2)
    - Central Intelligence Agency award ceremony for Edward P. Boland, Washington, D.C., 1985 December 16 (Box-folder 311: 3)
    - Christmas receptions, WJC residence, Washington, D.C., 1985 December 18-21 (Box-folder 311: 4)
    - Knights of Malta annual dinner, New York City, 1986 January 17 (Box-folder 311: 5)
    - Reagan Administration Executive Forum, Washington, D.C., 1986 February 6 (Box-folder 311: 6)
    - Wedding anniversary dinner for Sophia Casey and WJC, Washington, D.C., 1986 March 1 (Box-folder 311: 7)
    - Visit to South Africa, 1986 March 9-12 (Box-folder 311: 8)
    - Gridiron Club dinners and receptions hosted by major newspapers, Washington, D.C., 1986 March 21-23 (Box-folder 311: 9)
    - Dinner in honor of John N. McMahon, Washington, D.C., 1986 April 9 (Box-folder 311: 10)
    - Congressional dinner in honor of John N. McMahon, Washington, D.C., 1986 April 30 (Box-folder 311: 11)
    - American Jewish Committee annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 May 15 (Box-folder 311: 12)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies International Councillors meeting on Soviet political developments, Washington, D.C., 1986 May 16 (Box-folder 311: 13)
    - Proposed trip to Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 May 23-24 (Box-folder 312: 1)
      Trip was canceled
    - Meeting with business leaders, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 May 24 (Box-folder 312: 2)
      Proposed speech
    - Southern Center for International Studies luncheon, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 May 24 (Box-folder 312: 3)
      Includes proposed speech
    - Air Forces Escape and Evasion Society dinner, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 May 24 (Box-folder 312: 4)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of Ronald Reagan, Washington, D.C., 1986 May 29 (Box-folder 312: 5)
    - Central Intelligence Agency ceremony and exhibition in honor of William J. Donovan, Washington, D.C., 1986 June 2 (Box-folder 312: 6)
    - Conference on the Commercial Aircraft Industry, Washington, D.C., 1986 June 11 (Box-folder 312: 7)
    - Proposed trip to Long Island, New York, 1986 June 11-12 (Box-folder 312: 8)
    - Society for Historians of American Foreign Relations annual meeting, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1986 June 25 (Box-folder 312: 9)
    - Rocky Mountains College Placement Association meeting, Snowmass, Colorado, 1986 July 30 (Box-folder 312: 10)
    - Meeting with business leaders, Denver, Colorado, 1986 July 30 (Box-folder 312: 11)
    - Central Intelligence Agency award ceremony for Barry Goldwater, Washington, D.C., 1986 August 4 (Box-folder 312: 12)
    - Retirement ceremony for Admiral E. A. Burkhalter, Washington, D.C., 1986 August 11 (Box-folder 312: 13)
    - American Bar Association convention panel on terrorism, New York City, 1986 August 11 (Box-folder 312: 14)
    - Vacation trip to Ontario, Maine and Missouri, 1986 August 16-September 1 (Box-folder 312: 15)
    - American Business Conference luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 10 (Box-folder 312: 16)
    - Howard Taft Lecture, University Club, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 18 (Box-folder 312: 17)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. and William J. Donovan Foundation OSS/Donovan Symposium, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 19
      - Speech (Box-folder 312: 18)
      - Memoranda and background material for speech (Box-folder 313: 1)
    - Society of Professional Journalists meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 24 (Box-folder 313: 2)
    - Washington Times Advisory Board and Editorial Board annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 25 (Box-folder 313: 3)
    - National Security Agency new building dedication, Fort Meade, Maryland, 1986 September 26 (Box-folder 313: 4)
    - Defense Intelligence Agency anniversary dinner, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D.C., 1986 September 26 (Box-folder 313: 5)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Economic Financial Issues Conference, New York City, 1986 October 24 (Box-folder 313: 6)
    - Commissioning ceremonies for U.S.S. Theodore Roosevelt, Newport News, Virginia, 1986 October 24-25 (Box-folder 313: 7)
    - John M. Ashbrook Center for Public Affairs Lecture, Ashland College, Ashland, Ohio, 1986 October 27 (Box-folder 313: 8)
    - Nassau County Council of Boy Scouts of America dinner, Woodbury, New York, 1986 November 6 (Box-folder 313: 9)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency conference luncheon, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 November 8 (Box-folder 313: 10)
    - Southern Center for International Studies meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 November 8 (Box-folder 314: 1)
    - Dinner with business leaders, Atlanta, Georgia, 1986 November 8 (Box-folder 314: 2)
    - Practising Law Institute Communications Law Conference, New York City, 1986 November 14 (Box-folder 314: 3)
    - Testimonial dinner for Robert C. Ames, La Salle University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1986 December 11 (Box-folder 314: 4)
  - Outgoing letters, chronologically arranged
    - 1981 February (Box-folder 314: 5)
    - 1981 March (Box-folder 314: 6)
    - 1981 April (Box-folder 314: 7)
    - 1981 May (Box-folder 314: 8)
    - 1981 June (Box-folder 315: 1)
    - 1981 July (Box-folder 315: 2)
    - 1981 August (Box-folder 315: 3)
    - 1981 September (Box-folder 315: 4)
    - 1981 October (Box-folder 315: 5)
    - 1981 November (Box-folder 315: 6)
    - 1981 December (Box-folder 315: 7)
    - 1982 January (Box-folder 315: 8)
    - 1982 February (Box-folder 315: 9)
    - 1982 March (Box-folder 315: 10)
    - 1982 April (Box-folder 315: 11)
    - 1982 May (Box-folder 315: 12)
    - 1982 June (Box-folder 316: 1)
    - 1982 July (Box-folder 316: 2)
    - 1982 August (Box-folder 316: 3)
    - 1982 September (Box-folder 316: 4)
    - 1982 October (Box-folder 316: 5)
    - 1982 November (Box-folder 316: 6)
    - 1982 December (Box-folder 316: 7)
    - 1983 January (Box-folder 316: 8)
    - 1983 February (Box-folder 316: 9)
    - 1983 March (Box-folder 316: 10)
    - 1983 April (Box-folder 316: 11)
    - 1983 May (Box-folder 316: 12)
    - 1983 June (Box-folder 316: 13)
    - 1983 July (Box-folder 316: 14)
    - 1983 August (Box-folder 316: 15)
    - 1983 September (Box-folder 316: 16)
    - 1983 October (Box-folder 316: 17)
    - 1983 November (Box-folder 317: 1)
    - 1983 December (Box-folder 317: 2)
    - 1984 January (Box-folder 317: 3)
    - 1984 February (Box-folder 317: 4)
    - 1984 March (Box-folder 317: 5)
    - 1984 April (Box-folder 317: 6)
    - 1984 May (Box-folder 317: 7)
    - 1984 June (Box-folder 317: 8)
    - 1984 July (Box-folder 317: 9)
    - 1984 August (Box-folder 317: 10)
    - 1984 September (Box-folder 317: 11)
    - 1984 October (Box-folder 317: 12)
    - 1984 November (Box-folder 318: 1)
    - 1984 December (Box-folder 318: 2)
    - 1985 January (Box-folder 318: 3)
    - 1985 February (Box-folder 318: 4)
    - 1985 March (Box-folder 318: 5)
    - 1985 April (Box-folder 318: 6)
    - 1985 May (Box-folder 318: 7)
    - 1985 June (Box-folder 318: 8)
    - 1985 July (Box-folder 318: 9)
    - 1985 August (Box-folder 318: 10)
    - 1985 September (Box-folder 318: 11)
    - 1985 October (Box-folder 318: 12)
    - 1985 November (Box-folder 318: 13)
    - 1985 December (Box-folder 318: 14)
    - 1986 January (Box-folder 318: 15)
    - 1986 February (Box-folder 318: 16)
    - 1986 March (Box-folder 318: 17)
    - 1986 April (Box-folder 319: 1)
    - 1986 May (Box-folder 319: 2)
    - 1986 June (Box-folder 319: 3)
    - 1986 July (Box-folder 319: 4)
    - 1986 August (Box-folder 319: 5)
    - 1986 September (Box-folder 319: 6)
    - 1986 October (Box-folder 319: 7)
    - 1986 November (Box-folder 319: 8)
    - 1986 December (Box-folder 319: 9)
    - 1987 January (Box-folder 319: 10)
    - 1987 February (Box-folder 319: 11)
  - Correspondence, alphabetically arranged
    - A (Box-folder 319: 12)
    - Abrams, Elliott (Box-folder 319: 13)
    - Adelman, Kenneth (Box-folder 319: 14)
    - Agnew, Harold M. (Box-folder 319: 15)
    - Allen, Richard V. (Box-folder 319: 16)
    - Ambrose, Myles J. (Box-folder 319: 17)
    - Amery, Julian (Box-folder 319: 18)
    - Andreas, Dwayne O. (Box-folder 319: 19)
    - Angleton, James J. (Box-folder 319: 20)
    - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box-folder 319: 21)
    - Armstrong, Anne (Box-folder 319: 22)
    - Asel, Arthur E. (Box-folder 319: 23)
    - Aydelotte, William (Box-folder 319: 24)
    - B (Box-folder 319: 25)
    - Barnett, Frank R. (Box-folder 320: 1)
    - Barreaux, Theodore C. (Box-folder 320: 2)
    - Becker, Ralph E. (Box-folder 320: 3)
    - Beichman, Arnold (Box-folder 320: 4)
    - Bendetsen, Karl R. (Box-folder 320: 5)
    - Bethell, Nicholas, Lord (Box-folder 320: 6)
    - Black, Theodore M. (Box-folder 320: 7)
    - Blankman, Howard M. (Box-folder 320: 8)
    - Boisi, James O. (Box-folder 320: 9)
    - Bourbon de Parme, Michel de (Box-folder 320: 10)
    - Brandeburg, Glen (Box-folder 320: 11)
    - Bross, John A. (Box-folder 320: 12)
    - Brown, Anthony Cave (Box-folder 320: 13)
    - Brown, Edward T. (Box-folder 320: 14)
    - Bruce, Evangeline (Box-folder 320: 15)
    - Brunie, Charles H. (Box-folder 320: 16)
    - Buckley, Daniel G. (Box-folder 320: 17)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 320: 18)
    - Budd, John F., Jr. (Box-folder 320: 19)
    - Burger, Warren (Box-folder 320: 20)
    - Burton, John C. (Box-folder 320: 21)
    - Bush, Prescott S., Jr. (Box-folder 320: 22)
    - C (Box-folder 320: 23)
    - Campana, Jerry J. (Box-folder 320: 24)
    - Campo, J. William (Box-folder 320: 25)
    - Carley, John H. (Box-folder 320: 26)
    - Carlucci, Frank (Box-folder 320: 27)
    - Carmen, Gerald P. (Box-folder 320: 28)
    - Casey, Bernadette (Box-folder 321: 1)
    - Casey, Lawrence W. (Box-folder 321: 2)
    - Casey, Thomas M. (Box-folder 321: 3)
    - Cashen, Henry C., II (Box-folder 321: 4)
    - Catacosinos, W. J. (Box-folder 321: 5)
    - Chambers, Frank G. (Box-folder 321: 6)
    - Chennault, Anna (Box-folder 321: 7)
    - Cherne, Leo
      - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 321: 8)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 321: 9)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 321: 10)
      - 1985 (Box-folder 321: 11)
      - 1986-1987 (Box-folder 321: 12)
    - Clark, William (Box-folder 322: 1)
    - Cline, Ray S. (Box-folder 322: 2)
    - Cohn, Roy M. (Box-folder 322: 3)
    - Colby, William E. (Box-folder 322: 4)
    - Colen, Sidney (Box-folder 322: 5)
    - Collins, John J. (Box-folder 322: 6)
    - Connally, John B. (Box-folder 322: 7)
    - Conroy, Thomas F. (Box-folder 322: 8)
    - Cooke, Lawrence H. (Box-folder 322: 9)
    - Corcoran, Thomas G. (Box-folder 322: 10)
    - Costello, Mary (Box-folder 322: 11)
    - Costick, Miles M. (Box-folder 322: 12)
    - Crozier, Brian (Box-folder 322: 13)
    - Cummings, James C., Jr. (Box-folder 322: 14)
    - Cuneo, Ernest (Box-folder 322: 15)
    - D (Box-folder 322: 16)
    - Dade, George C. (Box-folder 323: 1)
    - Dannemeyer, William E. (Box-folder 323: 2)
    - Dart, Justin (Box-folder 323: 3)
    - Dasher, Joseph (Box-folder 323: 4)
    - Deak, Nicholas L. (Box-folder 323: 5)
    - Dickey, Margaret L. (Box-folder 323: 6)
    - Dillon, Wilton S. (Box-folder 323: 7)
    - Dodds-Parker, Douglas (Box-folder 323: 8)
    - Dolan, Anthony R.
      - 1982-1983 (Box-folder 323: 9)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 323: 10)
      - 1985-1986 (Box-folder 323: 11)
    - Dolan, Patrick (Box-folder 323: 12)
    - Douglas, James J. (Box-folder 323: 13)
    - DuBrul, Stephen M., Jr. (Box-folder 323: 14)
    - Duggan, Edward L. (Box-folder 323: 15)
    - DuPont, Eugene, III (Box-folder 323: 16)
    - Du Pont, Pete (Box-folder 323: 17)
    - Dyson, John S. (Box-folder 323: 18)
    - E (Box-folder 323: 19)
    - Ehrlichman, John (Box-folder 324: 1)
    - Eierman, Warren H. (Box-folder 324: 2)
    - Evans, Thomas W. (Box-folder 324: 3)
    - F (Box-folder 324: 4)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr. (Box-folder 324: 5)
    - Farber, Jack (Box-folder 324: 6)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 324: 7)
    - Finch, Robert H. (Box-folder 324: 8)
    - Fischer, David C. (Box-folder 324: 9)
    - Fisher, Antony (Box-folder 324: 10)
    - Fisher, Max M. (Box-folder 324: 11)
    - Fitzpatrick, John P. (Box-folder 324: 12)
    - Flanigan, Peter M. (Box-folder 324: 13)
    - Foley, William T. (Box-folder 324: 14)
    - Forbes, Malcolm S. (Box-folder 324: 15)
    - Fowler, Mark S. (Box-folder 324: 16)
    - Frank, Benjamin (Box-folder 324: 17)
    - Frank, Danny (Box-folder 324: 18)
    - Friedman, Samuel J. (Box-folder 324: 19)
    - Frisby, Owen V. (Box-folder 324: 20)
    - Funk, Arthur L. (Box-folder 324: 21)
    - G (Box-folder 324: 22)
    - Gallo, Fernando (Box-folder 324: 23)
    - Gambino, Richard (Box-folder 324: 24)
    - Garrick, Robert (Box-folder 324: 25)
    - Gaut, Marvin J. (Box-folder 324: 26)
    - Gimpel, Jean (Box-folder 325: 1)
    - Gingrich, Newt (Box-folder 325: 2)
    - Goldsmith, James, Sir (Box-folder 325: 3)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 325: 4)
    - Golon, James V. (Box-folder 325: 5)
    - Goss, Peter J. (Box-folder 325: 6)
    - Gould, Joseph (Box-folder 325: 7)
    - Gould, Milton S. (Box-folder 325: 8)
    - Gowen, William (Box-folder 325: 9)
    - Graham, Bernard (Box-folder 325: 10)
    - Graham, Daniel O. (Box-folder 325: 11)
    - Grant, William R. (Box-folder 325: 12)
    - Gray, Robert K. (Box-folder 325: 13)
    - Greenberg, Maurice R. (Box-folder 325: 14-15)
    - Guillermin, Henri (Box-folder 325: 16)
    - H (Box-folder 325: 17)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box-folder 326: 1)
    - Hammer, Armand (Box-folder 326: 2)
    - Hammett, William M. H. (Box-folder 326: 3)
    - Hammonds, Oliver W. (Box-folder 326: 4)
    - Hanauer, Bernard (Box-folder 326: 5)
    - Hannaford, Peter D. (Box-folder 326: 6)
    - Hanning, Hugh (Box-folder 326: 7)
    - Harris, William R. (Box-folder 326: 8)
    - Haukelid, Knut (Box-folder 326: 9)
    - Hefner, Robert A., III (Box-folder 326: 10)
    - Helms, Richard (Box-folder 326: 11)
    - Hendriks, Warren K., Jr. (Box-folder 326: 12)
    - Hennelly, Edmund P. (Box-folder 326: 13)
    - Howley, John (Box-folder 326: 14)
    - Hrubý, Blahoslav (Box-folder 326: 15)
    - Hubbell, Harvey, IV (Box-folder 326: 16)
    - Hug, Arthur, Jr. (Box-folder 326: 17)
    - Hugel, Max (Box-folder 326: 18)
    - Hussein, King of Jordan (Box-folder 326: 19)
    - Hymoff, Edward (Box-folder 326: 20)
    - I (Box-folder 326: 21)
    - Iacocca, Lee A. (Box-folder 326: 22)
    - Irvine, Reed (Box-folder 326: 23)
    - Irving, David (Box-folder 326: 24)
    - J (Box-folder 326: 25)
    - James, E. Pendleton (Box-folder 326: 26)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box-folder 326: 27)
    - Jolis, Albert E. (Box-folder 326: 28)
    - Jonas, Gilbert (Box-folder 326: 29)
    - Juncker, Flemming (Box-folder 326: 30)
    - K (Box-folder 326: 31)
    - Kahn, David (Box-folder 327: 1)
    - Kalmbach, Herbert W. (Box-folder 327: 2)
    - Kellis, James G. (Box-folder 327: 3)
    - Kelly, W. Thomas (Box-folder 327: 4)
    - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 327: 5)
    - Kintner, William R. (Box-folder 327: 6)
    - Kirkland, Lane (Box-folder 327: 7)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 327: 8)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 327: 9)
    - Koch, Edward I. (Box-folder 327: 10)
    - Koltai, Steven R. (Box-folder 327: 11)
    - Kraft, Joseph (Box-folder 327: 12)
    - Kupferman, Theodore R. (Box-folder 327: 13)
    - L (Box-folder 327: 14)
    - Laffer, Arthur B. (Box-folder 327: 15)
    - Laird, Melvin R. (Box-folder 327: 16)
    - Landau, Ralph (Box-folder 327: 17)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 327: 18)
    - Langan, Richard (Box-folder 327: 19)
    - Langerman, Lenore (Box-folder 327: 20)
    - Laqueur, Walter (Box-folder 327: 21)
    - Lasky, Melvin J. (Box-folder 327: 22)
    - Lawless, Eugene T. (Box-folder 327: 23)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 327: 24)
    - LeBoutillier, John (Box-folder 327: 25)
    - Leibman, Morris I. (Box-folder 327: 26)
    - Leonard, Frank M. (Box-folder 328: 1)
    - Levenstein, Aaron (Box-folder 328: 2)
    - Lewis, Drew (Box-folder 328: 3)
    - Loeb, John L., Jr. (Box-folder 328: 4)
    - Loeb, Nackey S. (Box-folder 328: 5)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe (Box-folder 328: 6)
    - M (Box-folder 328: 7)
    - McCann, William E. (Box-folder 328: 8)
    - McClaughry, John (Box-folder 328: 9)
    - McClory, Robert (Box-folder 328: 10)
    - McCloy, John J. (Box-folder 328: 11)
    - McCone, John A. (Box-folder 328: 12)
    - McCrary, John Reagan (Box-folder 328: 13)
    - McGivern, Owen (Box-folder 328: 14)
    - McGowan, T. Sean (Box-folder 328: 15)
    - MacKenzie, John R. (Box-folder 328: 16)
    - McKinnon, Dan (Box-folder 328: 17)
    - McMahon, John N. (Box-folder 328: 18)
    - Marks, John B. (Box-folder 328: 19)
    - Marsh, John D. (Box-folder 328: 20)
    - Martin, David (Box-folder 328: 21)
    - Menges, Constantine (Box-folder 328: 22)
    - Merwin, John D. (Box-folder 328: 23)
    - Messing, F. Andy, Jr. (Box-folder 328: 24)
    - Meyer, Herbert E. (Box-folder 328: 25)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 328: 26)
    - Miller, William J. (Box-folder 328: 27)
    - Mills, Margaret (Box-folder 328: 28)
    - Morgan, William J. (Box-folder 329: 1)
    - Mostoff, Allan S. (Box-folder 329: 2)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P. (Box-folder 329: 3)
    - Murphy, Thomas S. (Box-folder 329: 4)
    - N (Box-folder 329: 5)
    - Needham, James J. (Box-folder 329: 6)
    - Nelson, Joni Lysett (Box-folder 329: 7)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 329: 8)
    - Nofziger, Lyn (Box-folder 329: 9)
    - Nowak, Jan (Box-folder 329: 10)
    - O (Box-folder 329: 11)
    - O'Brien, Thomas M. (Box-folder 329: 12)
    - Olmer, Lionel H. (Box-folder 329: 13)
    - Olson, John B. (Box-folder 329: 14)
    - Orechio, Frank A. (Box-folder 329: 15)
    - Owens, Hugh F. (Box-folder 329: 16)
    - P (Box-folder 329: 17)
    - Paffendorf, Carl G. (Box-folder 329: 18)
    - Persico, Joseph E. (Box-folder 329: 19)
    - Peterson, William H. (Box-folder 329: 20)
    - Pfautch, Roy (Box-folder 329: 21)
    - Podhoretz, Norman (Box-folder 329: 22)
    - Powell, Lewis (Box-folder 329: 23)
    - Prothroe, John E. (Box-folder 329: 24)
    - Q (Box-folder 330: 1)
    - Quinn, William W. (Box-folder 330: 2)
    - R (Box-folder 330: 3)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 330: 4)
    - Romanones, Aline, Condesa de (Box-folder 330: 5)
    - S (Box-folder 330: 6)
    - Showers, Donald M. (Box-folder 330: 7)
    - Silberman, Laurence H. (Box-folder 330: 8)
    - Smith, Owen T. (Box-folder 330: 9)
    - V-W (Box-folder 330: 10)
    - Webster, William H. (Box-folder 330: 11)
  - Christmas card lists
    - 1982 (Box-folder 330: 12)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 330: 13)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 330: 14)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 330: 15)
  - Personal telephone directory (Box-folder 330: 16)
  - Reagan-Bush campaign anniversary address and telephone directories (Box-folder 330: 17)
  - White House telephone directory (Box-folder 330: 18)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 331: 1)
  - Publications (of the Central Intelligence Agency)
    - Directors and Deputy Directors of Central Intelligence: Dates and Data, 1946-1983 (Box-folder 331: 2)
    - Intelligence: The Acme of Skill (Box-folder 331: 3)
    - Intelligence in the War of Independence (Box-folder 331: 4)
    - USSR Energy Atlas (Box-folder 331: 5)
    - Career recruitment brochures (Box-folder 331: 6)
  - Publicity. Includes press coverage, press releases, and correspondence with and preparatory material relating to media
    - Biographical data (Box-folder 331: 7)
    - Biographical directory listings (Box-folder 331: 8)
    - Background biographical data (re WJC pre-Central Intelligence Agency) (Box-folder 331: 9)
    - Biographical miscellany (Box-folder 331: 10)
    - Interview requests declined (Box-folder 331: 11)
    - Press coverage
      - 1980 December (Box-folder 331: 12)
      - 1981 January (Box-folder 331: 13)
      - 1981 February (Box-folder 331: 14)
      - 1981 March (Box-folder 332: 1)
      - 1981 May (Box-folder 332: 2)
      - 1981 June (Box-folder 332: 3)
      - 1981 July (Box-folder 332: 4-6)
      - 1981 July (contd.) (Box-folder 333: 1)
      - Central Intelligence Agency press releases re resignation of Max Hugel and Senate Select Committee on Intelligence hearings, 1981 July (Box-folder 333: 2)
      - 1981 August (Box-folder 333: 3)
      - 1981 September (Box-folder 333: 4)
      - 1981 October (Box-folder 333: 5)
      - 1981 November (Box-folder 333: 6)
      - 1981 December (Box-folder 333: 7)
      - 1982 January (Box-folder 333: 8)
      - Interview with Newsday. Typed transcript, 1982 January 18 (Box-folder 333: 9)
      - 1982 February (Box-folder 333: 10)
      - 1982 March (Box-folder 334: 1)
      - Interview with U.S. News and World Report. Printed transcript, 1982 March 8 (Box-folder 334: 2)
      - Interview with Time. Preparatory materials for interview of, 1982 March 31 (Box-folder 334: 3)
      - 1982 April (Box-folder 334: 4)
      - Interview with Ralph Nader and Ron Brownstein for projected book. Preparatory materials for interview of, 1982 April 16 (Box-folder 334: 5)
      - 1982 May (Box-folder 334: 6)
      - 1982 June (Box-folder 334: 7)
      - 1982 July (Box-folder 334: 8)
      - 1982 August (Box-folder 334: 9)
      - 1982 September (Box-folder 334: 10)
      - 1982 October (Box-folder 334: 11)
      - Letter to the editors of the New York Times, Chicago Tribune and Philadelphia Inquirer by WJC re Freedom of Information Act. Printed copies, 1982 October 7 (Box-folder 334: 12)
      - Interview with Christian Science Monitor. Typed transcript, 1982 October 18, and resultant series of printed articles, 1982 October 28-December 8 (Box-folder 334: 13)
      - 1982 December (Box-folder 334: 14)
      - 1983 January (Box-folder 334: 15)
      - Interview with Los Angeles Times. Preparatory materials for interview of 1982 November 17, typed transcript, and resultant printed article, 1983 January 3 (Box-folder 334: 16)
      - Interview with New York Times Magazine. Preparatory materials for interview of 1982 November, and resultant printed article, 1983 January 16 (Box-folder 334: 17)
      - 1983 February (Box-folder 334: 18)
      - 1983 April (Box-folder 334: 19)
      - 1983 May (Box-folder 334: 20)
      - Press release by WJC re Nicaragua, 1983 May 23, and printed copy, 1983 May 24 (Box-folder 334: 21)
      - 1983 June (Box-folder 334: 22)
      - 1983 July (Box-folder 334: 23)
      - 1983 September (Box-folder 334: 24)
      - Interview with Washington Post. Preparatory materials for interview of 1983 August, and resultant printed article, 1983 September 7 (Box-folder 334: 25)
      - 1983 October (Box-folder 335: 1)
      - Interview with Newsweek. Preparatory and background materials for interview of 1983 August, and resultant printed article, 1983 October 10 (Box-folder 335: 2)
      - Letter to the editor of Newsweek by WJC re article of 1983 October 10. Typescript and printed copy, 1983 October 17 (Box-folder 335: 3)
      - 1983 November (Box-folder 335: 4)
      - Interview with New Republic. Preparatory materials for interview of 1983 October 1, and resultant printed article, 1983 November 28 (Box-folder 335: 5)
      - 1983 December (Box-folder 335: 6)
      - Interview with USA Today. Printed transcript, 1983 December 20 (Box-folder 335: 7)
      - 1984 January (Box-folder 335: 8)
      - 1984 February (Box-folder 335: 9)
      - 1984 March (Box-folder 335: 10)
      - 1984 April (Box-folder 335: 11)
      - Central Intelligence Agency press releases re news coverage of Nicaragua, 1984 April (Box-folder 335: 12)